♪ ♪
♪ YOU PROLLY THINK THAT YOU
ARE BETTER NOW, BETTER NOW ♪
♪ YOU ONLY SAY THAT 'CAUSE
I'M NOT AROUND, NOT AROUND ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I NEVER MEANT TO
LET YOU DOWN, LET YOU DOWN ♪
♪ WOULDA GAVE YOU ANYTHING,
WOULDA GAVE YOU EVERYTHING ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I SAY THAT I
AM BETTER NOW, BETTER NOW ♪
♪ I ONLY SAY THAT 'CAUSE YOU'RE
NOT AROUND, NOT AROUND ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I NEVER MEANT TO
LET YOU DOWN, LET YOU DOWN ♪
♪ WOULDA GAVE YOU ANYTHING,
WOULDA GAVE YOU EVERYTHING ♪
♪ OH-OH ♪
♪ I DID NOT BELIEVE
THAT IT WOULD END, NO ♪
♪ EVERYTHING CAME SECOND
TO THE BENZO ♪
♪ YOU'RE NOT EVEN
SPEAKIN' TO MY FRIENDS, NO ♪
♪ YOU KNEW ALL MY UNCLES
AND MY AUNTS THOUGH ♪
♪ TWENTY CANDLES, BLOW 'EM
OUT AND OPEN YOUR EYES ♪
♪ WE WERE LOOKIN' FORWARD
TO THE REST OF OUR LIVES ♪
♪ USED TO KEEP MY PICTURE
POSTED BY YOUR BEDSIDE ♪
♪ NOW IT'S IN YOUR DRESSER
WITH THE SOCKS YOU DON'T LIKE ♪
♪ AND I'M ROLLIN', ROLLIN',
ROLLIN', ROLLIN' ♪
♪ WITH MY BROTHERS
LIKE IT'S JONAS, JONAS ♪
♪ DRINKIN' HENNY
AND I'M TRYNA FORGET ♪
♪ BUT I CAN'T GET THIS
SHIT OUTTA MY HEAD ♪
♪ YOU PROLLY THINK THAT YOU
ARE BETTER NOW, BETTER NOW ♪
♪ YOU ONLY SAY THAT 'CAUSE
I'M NOT AROUND, NOT AROUND ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I NEVER MEANT TO
LET YOU DOWN, LET YOU DOWN ♪
♪ WOULDA GAVE YOU ANYTHING,
WOULDA GAVE YOU EVERYTHING ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I SAY THAT I
AM BETTER NOW, BETTER NOW ♪
♪ I ONLY SAY THAT 'CAUSE
YOU'RE NOT AROUND, NOT AROUND ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I NEVER MEANT TO
LET YOU DOWN, LET YOU DOWN ♪
♪ WOULDA GAVE YOU ANYTHING,
WOULDA GAVE YOU EVERYTHING ♪
♪ OH-OH ♪
♪ I SEEN YOU WITH
YOUR OTHER DUDE ♪
♪ HE SEEMED LIKE
HE WAS PRETTY COOL ♪
♪ I WAS SO BROKEN OVER YOU ♪
♪ LIFE IT GOES ON,
WHAT CAN YOU DO? ♪
♪ I JUST WONDER
WHAT IT'S GONNA TAKE
(WHATS IT GONNA TAKE) ♪
♪ ANOTHER FOREIGN OR
A BIGGER CHAIN
(BIGGER CHAIN) ♪
♪ BECAUSE NO MATTER HOW MY LIFE
HAS CHANGED (NO MATTER
HOW MY LIFE HAS CHANGED) ♪
♪ I KEEP ON LOOKING
BACK ON BETTER DAYS ♪
♪ YOU PROLLY THINK THAT YOU
ARE BETTER NOW, BETTER NOW ♪
♪ YOU ONLY SAY THAT 'CAUSE
I'M NOT AROUND, NOT AROUND ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I NEVER MEANT TO
LET YOU DOWN, LET YOU DOWN ♪
♪ WOULDA GAVE YOU ANYTHING,
WOULDA GAVE YOU EVERYTHING ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I SAY THAT I
AM BETTER NOW, BETTER NOW ♪
♪ I ONLY SAY THAT 'CAUSE
YOU'RE NOT AROUND, NOT AROUND ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I NEVER MEANT TO
LET YOU DOWN, LET YOU DOWN ♪
♪ WOULDA GAVE YOU ANYTHING,
WOULDA GAVE YOU EVERYTHING ♪
♪ OH-OH ♪
♪ I PROMISE ♪
♪ I SWEAR TO YOU,
I'LL BE OKAY ♪
♪ YOU'RE ONLY THE
LOVE OF MY LIFE
(LOVE OF MY LIFE) ♪
♪ YOU PROLLY THINK THAT YOU
ARE BETTER NOW, BETTER NOW ♪
♪ YOU ONLY SAY THAT 'CAUSE
I'M NOT AROUND, NOT AROUND ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I NEVER MEANT TO
LET YOU DOWN, LET YOU DOWN ♪
♪ WOULDA GAVE YOU ANYTHING,
WOULDA GAVE YOU EVERYTHING ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I SAY THAT I
AM BETTER NOW, BETTER NOW ♪
♪ I ONLY SAY THAT 'CAUSE
YOU'RE NOT AROUND, NOT AROUND ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I NEVER MEANT TO
LET YOU DOWN, LET YOU DOWN ♪
♪ WOULDA GAVE YOU ANYTHING,
WOULDA GAVE YOU EVERYTHING ♪
♪ OH-OH ♪
♪ ♪