WHAT UP MAN
WHAT UP BRO
EVERYTHING GOOD?
BLESS
HOW YOU BEEN?
I'M FREAKING AWESOME
♪ ♪
♪ MY MOMMA CALLED,
SEE YOU ON TV SON ♪
♪ SAID SHIT DONE CHANGED
EVER SINCE WE WAS ON ♪
♪ I DREAMED IT ALL EVER
SINCE I WAS YOUNG ♪
♪ THEY SAID I WOULD
BE NOTHING ♪
♪ NOW THEY ALWAYS SAY
CONGRATULATIONS ♪
♪ WORKED SO HARD, FORGOT
HOW TO VACATION ♪
♪ THEY AIN'T NEVER HAD
THE DEDICATION ♪
♪ PEOPLE HATIN' SAID WE
CHANGING LOOK WE MADE IT ♪
♪ YEAH WE MADE IT ♪
♪ THEY WAS NEVER FRIENDLY ♪
♪ NOW I'M JUMPING
OUT THE BENTLEY ♪
♪ AND I KNOW I
SOUND DRAMATIC ♪
♪ BUT I KNOW I
HAD TO HAVE IT ♪
♪ FOR THE MONEY
I'M A SAVAGE ♪
♪ GOT ME ITCHIN
LIKE A ADDICT ♪
♪ I'M SURROUNDED
BY 20 BAD BITCH ♪
♪ BUT THEY DIDN'T
KNOW ME LAST YEAR ♪
♪ EVERYONE WANT TO ACT
LIKE THEY IMPORTANT ♪
♪ BUT ALL THAT MEAN NOTHING
WHEN I SWANG MY DOOR ♪
♪ EVERYONE COUNTING ON
ME DROP THE BALL ♪
♪ EVERYTHING CUSTOM LIKE
I'M AT THE BORDER ♪
♪ IF YOU FUCK WITH WINNING BUT
YOUR LIGHTERS TO THE SKY ♪
♪ HOW COULD I MAKE CENTS WHEN
I GOT MILLIONS ON MY MIND ♪
♪ COMING WITH THAT BULLSHIT
I JUST PUT IT TO THE SIDE ♪
♪ BALLING SINCE A BABY, THEY
CAN SEE IT IN MY EYES ♪
♪ MY MOMMA CALLED, SEE
YOU ON TV SON ♪
♪ SAID SHIT DONE CHANGED
EVER SINCE WE WAS ON ♪
♪ I DREAMED IT ALL EVER
SINCE I WAS YOUNG ♪
♪ THEY SAID I
WOULD BE NOTHING ♪
♪ NOW THEY ALWAYS SAY
CONGRATULATIONS ♪
♪ WORKED SO HARD, FORGOT
HOW TO VACATION ♪
♪ THEY AIN'T NEVER HAD
THE DEDICATION ♪
♪ PEOPLE HATIN' SAID WE
CHANGING LOOK WE MADE IT ♪
♪ YEAH WE MADE IT ♪
♪ I WAS PATIENT ♪
♪ NOW I CAN SCREAM
THAT WE MADE IT ♪
♪ NOW EVERYWHERE EVERYWHERE I
GO THEY SAY CONGRATULATIONS ♪
♪ YOUNG N R YOUNG
N R GRADUATION ♪
♪ I PICK UP THE ROCK
AND I BALL BABY ♪
♪ I'M LOOKING FOR
SOMEONE TO CALL BABY ♪
♪ BUT RIGHT NOW I GOT
A SITUATION ♪
♪ NEVER OLD BEEN BEN
FRANKLINS ♪
♪ BIG RINGS, CHAMPAGNE, MY
LIFE IS LIKE A BALL GAME ♪
♪ BUT INSTEAD I'M IN
THE TRAP THOUGH ♪
♪ POT SO BIG CALL IT
SUPERBOWL, SUPERBOWL ♪
♪ SUPERBOWL CALL THE
HOES GET IN THE ROLLS ♪
♪ TOP FLOOR LIFESTYLE,
HUNCHO AND POST MALONE ♪
♪ I GOTTA PLAY
ON MY PHONE ♪
♪ YOU KNOW WHAT I'M ON ♪
♪ HUNCHO HOUDINI IT'S GONE ♪
♪ MY MOMMA CALLED, SEE
YOU ON TV SON ♪
♪ SAID SHIT DONE CHANGED
EVER SINCE WE WAS ON ♪
♪ I DREAMED IT ALL EVER
SINCE I WAS YOUNG ♪
♪ THEY SAID I
WOULD BE NOTHING ♪
♪ NOW THEY ALWAYS SAY
CONGRATULATIONS ♪
♪ WORKED SO HARD, FORGOT
HOW TO VACATION ♪
♪ THEY AIN'T NEVER HAD
THE DEDICATION ♪
♪ PEOPLE HATIN' SAID WE
CHANGING LOOK WE MADE IT ♪
♪ YEAH WE MADE IT ♪
♪♪♪