COME ON
NO
WE GOTTA GET OUTTA HERE
COME ON
♪♪♪
♪ ME AND KURT FEEL THE SAME ♪
♪ TOO MUCH PLEASURE IS PAIN ♪
♪ MY GIRL SPITES ME IN VAIN ♪
♪ ALL I DO IS COMPLAIN ♪
♪ SHE NEEDS
SOMETHING TO CHANGE ♪
♪ NEED TO TAKE
OFF THE E-E-EDGE ♪
♪ SO FUCK IT ALL TONIGHT ♪
♪ AND DON'T TELL ME TO SHUT UP ♪
♪ WHEN YOU KNOW YOU TALK TOO
MUCH ♪
♪ BUT YOU DON'T GOT SHIT TO
SAY-AY-AY ♪
♪ I WANT YOU OUT OF MY HEAD ♪
♪ I WANT YOU OUT OF MY
BEDROOM TONIGHT (BEDROOM) ♪
♪ THERE'S NO WAY I
COULD SAVE YOU (SAVE YOU) ♪
♪ CAUSE I NEED TO BE SAVED TOO ♪
♪ I'M NO GOOD AT GOODBYES ♪
♪ WE'RE BOTH ACTIN INSANE ♪
♪ BUT TOO STUBBORN TO CHANGE ♪
♪ NOW I'M DRINKIN AGAIN ♪
♪ 80 PROOF IN MY VEINS ♪
♪ AND MY FINGERTIPS STAINED ♪
♪ LOOKING OVER THE E-E-EDGE ♪
♪ DON'T FUCK WITH ME TONIGHT ♪
♪ SAY YOU NEEDED THIS HEART ♪
♪ THEN YOU GOT IT (GOT IT) ♪
♪ TURNS OUT THAT ♪
♪ IT WASN'T WHAT
YOU WANTED (WANTED) ♪
♪ AND WE WOULDN'T LET GO ♪
♪ AND WE LOST IT ♪
♪ NOW I'M A GONER ♪
♪ I WANT YOU OUT
OF MY HEAD (HEAD) ♪
♪ I WANT YOU OUT OF MY ♪
♪ BEDROOM TONIGHT (BEDROOM) ♪
♪ THERE'S NO WAY ♪
♪ I COULD SAVE YOU (SAVE YOU) ♪
♪ CAUSE I NEED TO BE
SAVED TOO (SAVED TOO) ♪
♪ I'M NO GOOD AT GOODBYES ♪
♪ I WANT YOU RIGHT IN MY LIFE ♪
♪ I WANT YOU BACK HERE TONIGHT ♪
♪ I'M TRYNA CUT YOU, NO KNIFE ♪
♪ I WANNA SLICE YA AND DICE YA ♪
♪ MY ARGUE POSSESSIVE ♪
♪ AIN'T GOT YOU PRECISE ♪
♪ CAN YOU NOT TURN OFF THE TV? ♪
♪ I'M WATCHIN A FIGHT ♪
♪ MY FLIGHT A GARAGE ♪
♪ BLUE DIAMOND, NO SHOCK ♪
♪ YOU POPPIN LIKE DOVE ♪
♪ THIS NIGGA BEIN HONEST ♪
♪ YOU DON'T NEED
A KEY TO DRIVE ♪
♪ YOUR CAR ON A CHARGER ♪
♪ I JUST WANNA SEE THE SIDE ♪
♪ THE ONE THAT'S
UNBOTHERED, YEAH ♪
♪ AND I DON'T WATCH YA ♪
♪ NEVER TO GO OUTSIDE (SIDE) ♪
♪ I PROMISE IF THEY PLAY ♪
♪ MY NIGGAS SLIDIN' (SLIDIN) ♪
♪ I'M FUCKIN IN HER TOO ♪
♪ BUT STILL RIDIN (RIDE IN) ♪
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ I WANT YOU OUT
OF MY HEAD (HEAD) ♪
♪ I WANT YOU OUT OF MY
BEDROOM TONIGHT (BEDROOM) ♪
♪ THERE'S NO WAY I
COULD SAVE YOU (SAVE YOU) ♪
♪ CAUSE I NEED TO BE
SAVED TOO (SAVED TOO) ♪
♪ I'M NO GOOD AT GOODBYES ♪
♪ GOODBYE, GOODBYE, GOODBYE ♪
♪♪♪